翻译   草草
时间轴   Jessie
后期   饿得慌
顾问   老杜
鸣谢   忙成狗的网飞
鸣谢   阿小小海
俄语顾问   西摆
特效   草草
校对   草草
总监   草草
纸牌屋
第三季  第十集
罗纳德·H·布朗  美国常驻联合国代表团大楼
以色列实施禁飞区
你是哪里人  布朗先生
And where are you from, Mr. Brown?
谢尔登  先生  我是退休警员
Sheldon, sir. I'm a retired police officer.
那谢尔登一定是全州
Well, then I can only imagine that Sheldon must be
最安全的地方了
one of the safest places in this state.
我们尽力而为吧
We do our best.
但我儿子  他是海军陆战队  派驻在德怀尔营
But my son, he's a marine, stationed at Camp Dwyer.
他比我更能保护我们国家
He keeps our country safer than I do.
我和我妻子想问
Me and my wife were wondering,
如果他被派去约旦河谷
if he got sent over to the Jordan Valley,
这真能保护我们的安全吗
will that really keep us safer?
因为看起来  整个维和行动
Because it sure seems like the whole peacekeeping mission
只让局势更加危险了
is only making things more dangerous.
谢谢提问  可以给我吗
Thank you for that. May I?
首先  容我说
Well, first of all, let me say
我十分感激你儿子的奉献
how grateful I am for your son's service.
我知道大家都很感激
I know we all feel exactly the same way.
现在  我回答你的问题
And now, uh, let me try to answer your question.
俄方是否与我们产生了矛盾
Have we run into some difficulties with the Russians?
是的
Yes, we have.
以色列和巴勒斯坦之间是否关系紧张
Is there tension between the Israelis and the Palestinians?
没错
Absolutely.
但这正是此次行动如此重要的原因
But, that is the very reason that this mission is so important.
我们集结了一支七国联合军队
We have gathered together a coalition of seven nations
稳定一个数十载
to bring stability to a region
动荡不安的地区
that has suffered from unrest for decades.
这自然需要时间
It will take time.
可能会有人牺牲
And there may be lives that will be lost.
但这不仅仅事关中东安定
But this is not just important for the Middle East's security,
也关系到美国
it's important for the security
和整个世界的安全
of the United States and the rest of the world.
希望你的问题得到了解答
And I hope that I've answered your question.
下面谁来
Now, who was next?
我看看
Uh, let's see here.
这位年轻的小姐吧
Well, how about this young woman right here?
我把麦克风给你
Now, I'll give you my microphone,
但你得答应会还给我
but only if you promise to give it back.
他似乎不怎么想给我呢
He seemed to want to hang onto it for a while.
-给  -我叫安妮·怀茨
- There you are. - Um, my name is Annie Wietz,
我也担心那位警官所说的事
and I'm also worried about what the officer was just saying.
我希望我孙辈能生活在安全的世界里
I want a safe world for my grandkids--
把麦克风给我  我回答你
Give me back the mic - and I'll answer your question.
我还没提问呢
No, sir. I haven't asked my question yet.
抱歉  我着急了  请
Apologies. I'm ahead of myself. Go ahead.
那项秘密行动  导致以色列入境的
The covert operation, the one that caused the Israelis to invade.
是我们吗  因为看起来
Was that us? Because that really seemed
那事把情况搞得一团糟
to make a mess of everything.
-可以给我吗  -请
- May I? - Please.
谢谢  安妮
Thank you. Now, Annie?
-是安妮吧  -是  先生
- Is that your name, yeah? - Yes, sir.
这事我已经说过了
Now, I have said this on this matter before,
我知道大家或许有不满  但事实如此
and I know it may be frustrating, but it is the truth.
对任何国家的秘密行动
When it comes to covert operations by any nation,
或情报问题  出于安全考虑
or matters of intelligence, for security purposes,
也包括我们本国战士的安全
including the security of our own soldiers,
我实在不能发表评论
I simply cannot comment on these issues.
但是  先生  抱歉
But, sir, I'm sorry,
如果你不肯回答
but what is the point of having us ask questions
-我们还何必提问  -被她说着了
- if you won't answer them? - Well, she's got me there. Uh...
除了这个问题我都能回答
I can answer any question but that one.
事实上  希望大家能问问
In fact, I hope that we can ask some questions about
我们要如何解决国内的一些问题
how we're gonna focus on things right here at home.
楼上二等座的人来问吧
How about someone up there in the cheap seats?
有人想问吗
Anyone have a question there?
约旦河谷的局势
The situation in Jordan Valley,
可能会引起境外流血冲突
it threatens to bleed across the border.
已经有难民请求进入约旦了
We already have refugees requesting to enter Jordan.
抱歉  里亚德王子
Forgive me, Prince Ryad.
你们虽然要应付几百个难民
You may be dealing with a few hundred refugees,
但我们可是要面对迫击炮袭击
but we are facing mortar attacks.
这两周就发生了14起
Fourteen in the last two weeks.
你们还没死人呢
None of your people have died yet.
最后的一次  离一所学校只有50米
The last one came within 50 meters of a school.
你们的军队袭击民宅  杀死了十数名巴勒斯坦人
Your troops have killed over a dozen Palestinians in house raids.
你还指望我们不还击吗
You expect us not to fight back?
暴力冲突必须停止
We need the violence to stop.
如果继续下去  维和任务会分崩离析
If it continues, the peacekeeping mission will fall apart.
而维和任务是长久稳定的最佳机会
And it's our best hope for long-term stability.
你能跟哈马斯和真主党沟通吗
Can you speak to Hamas and Hezbollah?
让他们同意停火
Get them to agree to a cease-fire?
以色列自维和任务开始后
Israel has twice as many troops in the region
在当地的驻军翻了一番
as before the peacekeeping mission began.
不  我们才是在自卫
No, it is we who are defending ourselves.
你答应撤离两千士兵了
You agreed to remove two thousand troops.
如果迫击炮袭击停止
If there's a cessation of mortar attacks,
如果俄军离开
and if the Russians leave.
派军削减三分之一
A one-third troop reduction.
这足以说服你们的人了吧
That should be enough to convince your people, no?
等以军离开  我再去找他们  之前不行
Once the troops leave, I engage them, but not before.
显示点诚意吧  就算到时你还有四千士兵呢
Show some goodwill. You'll still have 4,000 troops there.
因为这样下去将毫无进展
Because we cannot accomplish anything
除非能证明双方都愿缓和局势
unless we have proof of de-escalation on both sides.
那俄国呢
What about Russia?
这是另外的问题了  我们改日再解决
That's a separate issue. We will tackle that another time.
你能向耶路撒冷转达
Can you convey to Jerusalem
此次部分撤军的重要性吗
the importance of this troop reduction?
可以  但结果无法保证
Yes, but no promises.
好吧  谢谢各位
All right. Thank you, everyone.
我们明早再会面
We'll meet again tomorrow morning.
谢谢  夫人
Thank you, madam.
伊莉安娜
Eliana.
我们得讨论禁飞区的问题
We need to discuss the no-fly zone.
那是给俄国人定的  不是维和军
It's only for the Russians, not the peacekeepers.
他们如果断了粮  就待不下去
They can't stay if they have nothing to eat.
你打算怎么做  把供给货机打下来吗
What are you going to do, shoot down a supply plane?
希望他们不会逼我们做这个选择
We hope they won't make us face that choice.
他们会无视的
They'll ignore it.
你这样只会激怒莫斯科
And you're just going to antagonize Moscow.
抱歉  但禁飞区的事是上方定下的
I'm sorry, but the no-fly zone is above my pay grade.
或许你丈夫可以去跟总理谈谈
Perhaps your husband can talk to the prime minister.
什么时候开始
When are we looking at?
或许是明天  或许一周后
Could be tomorrow, could be a week.
那些事已经轮不到我插嘴了
I'm not a part of those conversations anymore.
我们可以审查问题
We could vet the questions.
那在爱荷华州行不通  只会激起民愤
That doesn't work in Iowa. It'll piss people off.
即便如此也无济于事
Even if we did, it wouldn't make a difference.
整个国家的心思都在约旦河谷上
The country is preoccupied with the Jordan Valley.
话题完全跑偏了
We're off message.
现在
In the meantime,
我们可以暂停市政厅集会  只做巡回宣传
we can put the town halls on hold. Just do the stump.
我觉得辩论也最好延迟
I think we should also postpone the debate.
邓巴会为此狠狠攻击你  说你在回避
Dunbar'll hit you hard for that. Say you're dodging.
那让杰姬提出推迟
Have Jackie request the postponement.
-什么理由  -我不管
- What's her reason? - I don't care.
只要不是我们提出来就行
Just as long as it isn't coming from us.
跟她谈谈  谢谢了  各位
Talk to her. Thank you, gentlemen.
接下来什么事
What's next?
为竞选筹款打电话  直到4点15
Uh, you're slated for fundraising calls until 4:15,
然后是国防部的简报
then a DOD briefing.
另外  你桑蒂诺的朋友  蒂姆·科贝特打来了
Also, your friend from The Sentinel called, Tim Corbet.
谢谢
Thank you.
我自己会叠衣服
You know, I can fold my own clothes.
不费事
Took me two seconds.
记得我大四那年我们睡一间房吗
You remember when we shared a room my senior year?
我要是把一只袜子丢在地板上  你就会抓狂
And if I left, like, one sock on the floor, you'd freak?
我后来开始有意那么做  好看你发火
Yeah, I started doing that on purpose, just to see you flip out.
嗯  我记得
Yeah. I remember.
得了  别管了  随意点
Come on, leave it. Be a rebel.
亲爱的
Hey, sweetie.
告诉她如果动了  就是要掉了
Well, tell her if it wiggles, it means it's gonna fall out.
好  让她听
Okay. Let me talk to her.
听我说
Uh, now, listen to me. You--
我知道你妈妈不让你动
I know your mom doesn't want you playing with it,
你得听她话
so you have to do what she says.
因为牙仙不喜欢上面沾满指纹
Well, because the tooth fairy doesn't want fingerprints all over it.
好  我答应  但你保证
Okay, I'll do it, but you have to promise me
你和你弟弟都不会再摆弄牙了
that you and your brother will stop playing with your tooth.
好  准备好了吗
Okay, you ready?
真的准备好了吗
Are you super ready?
咪咪喵  咪咪喵  咪咪喵
Boogala, boogala, boogala, boogala, boogala.
好了  让妈妈听
Okay. Put your mom back on.
推迟多久
How much of a postponement?
直到我们解决危机
Until we get this crisis resolved.
邓巴一眼就看穿了
Dunbar will see right through that.
除非是你说
Not if it's coming from you.
就说你现在想当面接触民众
Say you want to focus on meeting people face to face,
而不是电视辩论
not a televised debate.
我们会支持你
We'll back you up.
好  我跟我手下谈谈
All right, I'll talk to my staff.
我们起草一下言辞  再给你看一下
We'll draft some language and I'll run it past you.
杰姬
Jackie?
我想跟你谈谈两周前的那件事
I want to talk to you about what happened a couple weeks ago.
-我越界了  -雷米  你不用解释
- I crossed a line. - Remy, you don't have to.
我想解释一下
I want to. I want to explain myself.
我对你还有感觉  这我不否认
I still have strong feelings, I'm not gonna deny that.
如果情况不同  我不做这个
Maybe a different job... A different time, different place.
可是...
But, uh...
听我说
Look...
我以前也放下过曾经爱过的人
I've loved people before, and I've learned to let 'em go.
我再不会让你为难了
I'm not gonna put you in that position again.
对我也不容易
It's been hard for me, too.
你还有工作
You've got work.
我很高兴你说出来了
I'm glad you said something.
喂
Hello?
蒂姆  是弗兰克
Tim, it's Frank.
抱歉这么晚才回你电话
I'm sorry it took me all day to get back to you.
没事  你现在一定忙死了
Ah, no worries. Your plate must be pretty full.
我的确希望能没这么多事
Well, more than I'd like at the moment.
打扰你了吗
Is this a bad time?
我还是能腾出点时间
I think I can spare a few minutes
跟美国总统通话的
for the President of the United States.
-你好吗  -挺好
- Are you good? - Yeah.
最后一个孩子也去大学了
Good. Uh, last kid got off to college,
家里就剩贝丝和我了
so Beth and I are on our own.
总算  生意不错
Finally. Yeah, the business is strong.
我还打算扩张到格伦伍德峡谷呢
I'm actually, uh, I'm thinking of expanding to Glenwood Canyon.
那好啊
That's great.
听我说  我打给你是因为
Listen, I called because that,
那个作者来找我了
that writer reached out to me.
给你写书的那个
You know, the one doing your book.
说要跟我谈谈桑蒂诺的事
Said, uh, he wanted to talk about The Sentinel.
你怎么说的
What'd you say?
我说我有点急事  回头打给他
I said I was in a rush and I'd call him back later.
没跟你商量过  我不想多说什么
I didn't want to say more without talking to you first.
他应该先问我的
Well, he should've checked with me beforehand.
我可不希望他去骚扰我的朋友
I don't want him harassing my friends.
他倒是没有骚扰我  他人不错
He wasn't harassing me at all. He's a nice guy, actually.
如果对你的书有用  我乐意跟他谈
I mean, I'm happy to talk with him if it'll help your book.
这书不是讲桑蒂诺的
Well, the book isn't really about The Sentinel,
真不知他是何必
so I don't know why he'd bother,
但我会跟他谈谈  回头给你回复
but I'll talk to him and I'll let you know.
随你  总统先生
Whatever you need, Mr. President.
你够了
Stop that.
听我说  我们给三军统帅打对折
Hey, listen, uh, we run a half-price special for Commanders-in-Chief.
你什么时候来科罗拉多州
So, uh... if you're ever in Colorado
又有时间
with some time on your hands...
希望前总统也有这待遇
Well, I hope the same goes for ex-presidents, too.
不行  只针对在任总统  你最好拿下选举
Nope. Only sittin' ones. So you better win that damn election.
那我尽力  跟你聊天真愉快  蒂姆
I'll do my best. Nice talking to you, Tim.
我也是  弗兰克
You too, Frank.
单独安排汤姆·耶茨明天来见我
I want to set aside time for Tom Yates, in person. Tomorrow.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
嗯
Yes.
弗兰西斯
Francis?
我刚跟凯茜打完电话
I just got off the phone with Cathy.
以色列要实施禁飞区了
The Israelis are instituting the no-fly zone.
我安排了明天跟总理通话呢
I'm scheduled to have a call tomorrow with the prime minister.
他们要取消通话
They want to cancel the call.
我看看能不能现在接通他
Let me see if I can get him on the phone now.
他们已向所有大使馆发布了公告
They just sent out a communiqué to all embassies.
早上好
Good morning.
诸位...
As you--
抱歉  昨晚很繁忙
Excuse me. It's been a long night.
谢谢
Thank you.
以色列于当地时间今早6点  在约旦河谷上空
Israel instituted a no-fly zone over the Jordan Valley,
实施了禁飞区
6:00 a.m. today, Israeli time.
我虽然反对此举
And while I disagree with this action,
我能理解其初衷
I understand the reason behind it,
我们必须与同盟同一阵线
and we must stand with our ally.
我们的主要目标仍是缓和当地局势
Our chief goal remains de-escalation in the region.
安德伍德大使和国务院
Ambassador Underwood and the State Department
在与各相关方为此目标进行努力
are working with all interested parties toward that end.
我们的优先考虑是保证平民安全
Our utmost priority is guaranteeing civilian safety.
-以色列已经证实...  -什么时候去得梅因[爱荷华首府]
- And Israel has confirmed -When are you off to Des Moines?
两小时后  还得先给几个资助人打电话
A couple of hours. I have to make some donor calls first.
今天有手术吗
You have surgery today?
两个搭桥手术  明天三个
A double bypass. Triple tomorrow.
但之后一周几乎没什么安排
But nothing scheduled for almost a week after,
所以或许我可以去爱荷华州  我们...
so maybe I can come out to Iowa and we can--
-俄国飞机如无视...  -怎么了
- Russian aircrafts that ignore this... - What's going on?
可能遭受军事打击
...could potentially be subject to military action...
约旦河谷真是一团糟
This Jordan Valley thing's a mess.
他有大麻烦了
He's in big trouble.
...此类举动
...any such actions...
还有《美就法》那档子事
And then there's the whole AmWorks thing.
去年留下的包袱
All the baggage from last year.
-你后悔了吗  -不知道
- You having doubts? - I don't know.
或许吧
Maybe.
这好像挺严肃啊
That sounds serious.
如果说有抛弃他的理想时机  就是现在了
If there was an ideal time to walk away, now is it.
然后呢
And then what?
专心于国会
Focus on Congress.
但你的野心不止如此啊
Yeah, but you want more than that.
我可以多陪陪你和孩子
I could spend more time with you and the kids.
我不希望妻子
Well, I don't want a wife who's miserable
因为放弃了白宫而怨念不已
because she turned her back on the White House.
听我说
Look...
手术一旦开始  就不能停下
The thing about surgery is, once you're in, you're in.
你面前是一颗跳动的心脏  别人的生命
There's a beating heart in front of you. Someone's life.
不能有迟疑
There's no room for doubt.
不论出了什么问题
So, whatever goes wrong...
比如大出血  或者血块  也只能去应付
say hemorrhage or a blood clot, you deal with it.
你不能放弃
You don't get to walk away.
但那是生死大事  这不是
But that's life or death. This isn't.
对你来说是的
It is for you.
维持国际和平和稳定
...to maintain international peace and security.
美国决心解决当前事态
The United States is committed to defusing this situation.
我们会支持以色列  支持巴勒斯坦
We are here for Israel, we are here for Palestine,
也支持俄罗斯
we are here for Russia.
我们会...
And we are here for--
-可以去参加会面了吗  -嗯
- Ready to go to your meeting? - Yeah.
走吧
Come on.
我在想
I was thinking...
你前一阵
you know how a while back,
说要让孩子从俄亥俄州过来
you mentioned the kids coming out from Ohio?
你希望他们来吗
You want them to visit?
或许你不希望他们看到我这样
Well, maybe you don't want them to see me like this?
-复健  戒酒  -你表现一直很棒
- Doing my 60 days? - You've been doing great.
我当然乐意让他们来看叔叔
I'd be thrilled for them to come out here and meet their uncle,
如果你真想的话
if that's something you want to do.
我可以在沙发上睡几晚
I could hit the couch for a few nights.
你们睡卧房
You guys can have the bedroom.
我打给萨拉
I'll call Sarah.
我要对以色列说  留着你们的领空吧
I say to Israel, keep your airspace.
留着你们的禁飞区吧
Keep your no-fly zone.
我还是会飞过去
I will be flying through it, nevertheless.
你要是想  就把我打下来
Shoot me down, if you wish,
因为什么都别想阻止我
because nothing can stop me
去跟我的同胞站在一起
from standing side by side with my countrymen.
我要去拥抱为国奉献的士兵
I will embrace the men who serve this country,
因为我是俄国人
because I am Russian,
俄国人  不抛弃自己人
and Russians... do not abandon their own.
俄国电视台
Russian TV.
45分钟前  可能是大话
Forty-five minutes ago. It could be hot air.
佩特罗夫想让全世界都看到
Petrov wants the world to see this.
如果不是真心的  就不会公开放话
He wouldn't put it out there unless he meant it.
以色列说他们打算执行禁飞区令
Israel says they're prepared to enforce the no-fly zone.
他们不会把一国元首打下来的
They'll never shoot down a head of state.
那他们就会丢面子
Yeah, which means they'll lose face
进而增加派军  来挽回这个面子
and compensate by increasing their ground presence.
我让耶路撒冷同意部分撤军了
I got Jerusalem to agree to a pullout.
-两千士兵  -如果佩特罗夫飞过去就没戏了
- Two thousand troops. - Not if Petrov flies there.
如果我们把佩特罗夫的行为说成政治作秀
If we downplay Petrov's move as political theatrics,
我或许还能说服以色列人按原计划走
I might be able to convince the Israelis to follow through.
不行  我们得直接回应俄罗斯
No, we need to respond to Russia directly,
而不是跟以色列浪费时间
not waste our time with Israel.
以色列是我们的同盟  跟他们谈
Israel is our ally. We're far more likely
比跟俄罗斯谈更可能产生结果
to have a productive dialogue with them than with Russia.
对  但我们的主要目标是什么
Yes. What's our main objective here?
让俄军撤离约旦河谷
To get Russian troops out of the Jordan Valley.
我们别再拐弯抹角了
Let's stop poking around from the sides.
我们得正面面对问题
We need to tackle this head on.
跟莫斯科取得联系
Open up a line of communication with Moscow.
告诉他们我要亲自去约旦河谷
Tell them I'm coming to the Jordan Valley myself.
先生
Sir, I--
我要在当地跟佩特罗夫面谈
I'm gonna meet with Petrov face to face, on the ground.
-总统先生  这么做的风险  -我知道
- Mr. President, the risk factors of - I'm well aware.
佩特罗夫一动身就通知我
I want to be notified the moment that Petrov is on his way.
你跟中情局和国防部合作
You work with the CIA and DOD
解决一切必要后勤和安全问题
to figure out any logistics and security you have to.
找赛斯  开始起草措辞
Talk to Seth. Let's start drafting our message.
凯茜  我要跟你和国防部谈谈
Cathy, I want to sit down with you and Defense,
看我们有什么筹码
and work out bargaining chips.
谢谢各位
Thank you all very much.
马上行动
I meant now.
-不得打扰我  -您安排了跟耶茨先生的见面
- I'm not to be disturbed. - You have a meeting with Mr. Yates.
让他等  告诉他我得好一会儿
Have him wait and tell him it might be a while.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
莫里科夫大使为您接通了
You're on with Ambassador Moryakov.
-亚历克西  -你在浪费时间  克莱尔
- Alexi? - You're wasting your time, Claire.
我们不能让佩特罗夫去
We can't let Petrov go.
我无能为力
I'm powerless.
那告诉我能找谁去说动他
Then tell me who we can speak to who can influence him.
他心意已决  没人敢为此跟他唱反调
His mind is made up. No one would dare challenge him on this.
好吧  那我去纽约  我们见见卡斯皮
All right, then I'll come to New York. Let's meet with Caspi.
我们一起安抚耶路撒冷的担心
We'll ease Jerusalem's fears together.
不行  我正要去华盛顿
I can't. I'm on my way to Washington.
-为什么  -大使馆召我去
- What for? - The embassy sent for me.
我被召回了
I'm being recalled.
-是因为...  -我不知道
- Is it because...? - I don't know.
亚历克西  如果你需要什么
Alexi, if you need anything--
大使已经挂断  安德伍德夫人
The ambassador has ended the call, Mrs. Underwood.
-安德伍德夫人  -你好
- Mrs. Underwood. - Hello.
-艾德华  -稍等
- Edward? - Wait here a moment.
是  夫人
Yes, ma'am?
他来干什么
What's he doing here?
总统要见他
The president wanted to meet with him.
他叫我安排他去楼上等着
He asked me to have him wait upstairs.
-谢谢  -夫人
- Thank you. - Yes, ma'am.
如果他的要求还跟此前一样
If he wants the same terms as we had before,
我会努力说服我们北约的盟国
I'll smooth it over with our NATO allies.
失去波兰的确不妙  但我觉得芬兰海
It's tough to lose Poland, but I think that we can compensate
这里巡逻的反导弹潜艇可以起补偿作用
with anti-missile subs on patrol here in the Finnish Sea.
弗兰西斯  有空吗
Francis? Do you have a moment?
我就回来
I'll be right back.
让我们单独谈谈
Give us a minute.
我觉得这是个错误  你这是追他
I think this is a mistake. You're chasing him.
-让我去做以色列的工作  -你一直在做
- Let me work with Israel. - You've been working with Israel.
结果现在闹出个禁飞区  进一步  退两步
Now there's a no-fly zone. One step forward, two steps back.
外交需要时间
Diplomacy takes time.
爱荷华两个月后就投票了
Iowa is in two months.
你不能让竞选决定外交政策
You can't let the campaign drive our foreign policy.
如果我拿不下爱荷华  就没什么外交政策可言了
If I don't win in Iowa, there is no foreign policy.
抱歉  总统先生
Excuse us, Mr. President.
我们别在这儿说了
Let's not talk out here.
如果你去了约旦河谷
If you go to the Jordan Valley,
就必须谈出个结果来
you have to walk away with a solution.
他也知道  这样筹码就都在他手里了
And he knows that, which means he gets all the leverage.
我们现在也没什么筹码啊
Well, it's not as if we have much leverage at the moment.
他会希望中止维和任务
He's going to want the peacekeeping mission out.
没错  还有拆除导弹防御系统
That's right. And the missile defense system, too.
如果有必要  我两样都会满足他
And I'm prepared to give him both if necessary.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
别放弃维和任务  弗兰西斯
Don't toss the mission aside, Francis.
克莱尔  这事你太动感情
Claire, you're too invested in this.
维和任务已经完了
The mission is dead.
那些士兵炸死的时候就完了
It was dead the moment those troops got blown up.
你的计划失败了  很抱歉
Your plan failed. I'm sorry.
是我的错  是我批准了
It's my fault. I approved it.
但现在  我得去挽救
But now, I have to fix it.
你为什么不肯相信外交手段
Why won't you place faith in a diplomatic solution?
这就是外交
This is diplomacy.
有时候就得靠两个人  在一个房间里谈
Sometimes it comes down to two men in a room.
我现在对联合国已经不抱希望了
I have no faith in the UN anymore.
但我相信我可以跟此人谈妥
I do have faith in my ability to negotiate with this man.
弗兰西斯  我知道你看重我的想法
Francis, I know you value my opinion.
当然  超过一切
Absolutely, above all others.
我们对如何处理俄罗斯
We have both put a great deal of effort
都耗尽心思和努力
and thought into how to handle Russia.
我希望这次我们能共同做决定
I'd like for this to be a decision we make together,
而不是冲动地回应...
instead of an impulsive response--
-待会儿的  -佩特罗夫起飞了
- Not right now. - Petrov's in the air.
接戴尔海军上将
Get Admiral Dale on the line.
克莱尔  我看重你的想法
Claire, I value your opinion.
但我这次不认同你
I just don't agree with it this time.
耶茨先生
Mr. Yates.
总统只能重新安排了
The president's gonna have to reschedule.
托马斯
Thomas.
能让我们谈谈吗  艾德华
You give us a few moments, Edward?
是  夫人  我就在楼梯处
Yes, ma'am. I'll be by the stairs.
书写得如何了
How's the book coming?
我有点遇到障碍了
I've hit a bit of a roadblock.
缺失了很大一块
There's a big piece missing.
-是什么  -你
- What is it? - You.
他完全没提我吗
He hasn't... mentioned me at all?
提过很多  但不够
Plenty of times, but... it's not enough.
他怎么说的
What has he said?
你这让我很难做啊  安德伍德夫人
You're putting me in an awkward position, Mrs. Underwood.
你不想背叛他的信任
You don't want to betray his trust.
他和我有协议
He and I have an agreement.
我理解  我不该打听  我不打扰你了
I understand. I shouldn't pry. I'll leave you be, then.
他说他爱你超过一切
He said he loves you more than anything.
说没有你就不能入主白宫
That there wouldn't be a White House without you.
他带我去了加夫尼  你们第一个家
He showed me your first house... in Gaffney.
你种郁金香的地方
Where you planted the tulips.
他说他很羞耻
And he said he was ashamed.
为什么
Of what?
你嫁给了他  因为你能找更好的
That you married him. Because you deserve better.
你真的应该出现在这本书里  安德伍德夫人
You should really be in this book, Mrs. Underwood.
我有很多从他视角出发的故事
I've got a lot of stories from his perspective.
但没有一个是你的视角
Not a single one from yours.
是他要竞选总统啊  不是我
Well, he's the one running for president, not me.
嗯
Yeah.
我也说不好  或许是我错了
I don't know. Maybe I'm wrong.
我觉得人们要听听你的声音才能听到他的话
I think people need to hear your voice to hear his.
我们可以安排一次见面吗
Can we set up a time to meet?
我想想吧  谢谢你  托马斯
I'll think about it. Thank you, Thomas.
好吧
Okay.
赛斯  这不错  但再把期望降低一些
Seth, this is good, but downplay expectations even more.
结果还很难说呢
There's no telling what we'll walk away with.
-是  先生  -出于安全考虑
- Yes, sir. - We shouldn't inform the press
我们应该等您着陆再通知媒体
until after you land, for security purposes.
唐纳德
Donald...
-如果我出了事  -我准备好了
- If anything should happen to me - I'm prepared.
-但不会有事的  -上帝保佑
- But nothing will. - God help us.
丹顿会给你完整的情况报告
Danton will walk you through the full brief.
战况室都准备好了
Everything's set up in the Situation Room.
-好运  总统先生  -谢谢  我就回来
- Good luck, Mr. President. - Thank you. I'll be right back.
听我说  我知道你对此有反对
Now, listen, I know you have reservations about all this.
你在采取你认为最好的办法
You're doing what you think is best.
一定小心
Please be careful out there.
我会的
I will.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
走吧
Let's go.
有人吗
Hello?
你好  天呐  你们还真像
Hello! Wow! You guys really look alike!
好吧
Okay.
我们一家人喜欢抱抱
We're a hugging family.
看出来了
I see.
你是弗朗辛吧
Hi, you must be Francine.
-才不是  -她喜欢叫弗朗琪
- No, I'm not! - She likes Franke better.
认识你很高兴  弗朗琪
Nice to meet you, Franke.
-不要  -没错
- No. - Yep.
-我说了吧  -小心点
- I told you! - Careful.
-这是道格叔叔  -这是谁啊
- It's your Uncle Doug. - Hey, who's that?
要去跟道格叔叔抱抱吗
Do you want to give your Uncle Doug a hug?
过来
Come here, you.
我们会在特拉维夫市着陆
We'll land in Tel Aviv,
然后由特种部队护送
then take a special forces convoy
至河谷边界
from there to the perimeter of the valley.
到达河谷之前  以色列都会提供空中支援
The Israelis will provide air support until we get to the valley,
然后我们的直升机接手
then our helos will take over.
达到营地后
Once we get to the camp,
俄国人坚持我们只保留地面小队
the Russians insist on ground units only.
我们会通过一个检查点
We'll pass through a checkpoint--
这里有多安全
How secure is this location?
该地点的防守我们并不满意
The position is not fortified to our liking.
不能防爆
It's not blast-proof.
长官  我们要请您穿防弹衣戴头盔
Sir, we're going to ask that you wear your Kevlar and helmet.
先生
Sir?
玛丽
Mary.
为什么没有让记者随行
Why were no press allowed to go?
鉴于安全局势
Given the security situation,
我们不想让记者涉险
we didn't want to put any press in harm's way,
或冒险让敌方提前得知消息
or risk any hostile elements knowing in advance.
那么总统已经着陆了吗
So the president has already landed?
大概90分钟前
About 90 minutes ago.
马克
Mark.
总统究竟希望达成什么目的
What exactly does the president hope to achieve?
理想情况是俄方离开该地区
Ideally, we'd like the Russians to vacate the region.
但这无法保证
We can't promise that they will.
但总统希望
But the president hopes
我们能就撤兵取得进展
that we can make progress toward a withdrawal.
凯特
Kate.
这可被视为选举作秀
This could be seen as an election stunt.
他在民调中落后邓巴  所以想挽救大局
He's trailing Dunbar in the polls, so he wants to save the day.
我保证  这绝非作秀
I guarantee you this is no stunt.
总统为解决这一危机采取了非常手段
The president is taking extraordinary measures to end this crisis.
总统先生  您请
Господин президент, пожалуйста.
总统先生
Mr. President.
你现在可以脱下防弹衣了  总统先生
You can take your vest off now, Mr. President.
-这里很安全  -你相信这些墙吗
- We're safe here. - You trust these walls?
你要是害怕  就不该来
If you're frightened, you shouldn't have come.
我在克格勃的时候  在阿富汗待了六个月
When I was in the KGB, I spent six months in Afghanistan.
这地方比起
This place is a palace
我当时待的地洞简直是宫殿
compared to the hole in the ground I lived in.
来  你得保持水分
Here. You should stay hydrated.
-我用飞机拉来了一箱水  -谢谢
- I brought a shipment of water in on my plane. - Thank you.
以色列还说要断我们的补给呢
So much for the Israelis stopping our resupply.
真希望我们能处在河谷更肥沃的地带
I wish we were in the fertile part of the valley, though.
听说有些地方绿意盎然  十分美丽
I hear it's quite green and beautiful.
这里更合适拍照嘛
Well, this is better for pictures.
什么意思
How do you mean?
如果你飞去个天堂般的地方
Well, if you flew into a paradise,
那就没什么效果了  是吧
wouldn't be as effective, now, would it?
你这人的确有表演天赋
You do have a flair for the theatrical.
我也可以这么说你
I can say the same about you,
这样跑到我家门口
showing up on my doorstep like this.
这不是你家门口
This isn't your doorstep.
你跑到你不该来的地方了
You're squatting where you shouldn't be.
我觉得我的手下可不会那么看
I don't think my men will see it like that.
你的手下可知道
Do your men know that
是你杀了他们的同志
you're responsible for killing their comrades?
指责
Accusations.
你就打算拿这个说服我吗
That's how you plan to convince me?
你要什么才肯撤军
What do you require to pull out of the valley?
你方军队也离开
That your troops leave as well,
结束整个维和行动
and the entire peacekeeping operation.
只要俄军一撤离
Well, as soon as your troops withdraw,
我一定让联合国军队也撤走
I'll make sure the UN forces do exactly the same.
你还得削减导弹防御
And you scale back missile defense.
就像我们之前曾两次说好的那样
As we agreed to twice already.
当时我们的谈判可完全不同
That's when we were making an entirely different deal.
现在最大的区别是
The main difference now
如今我们都在沙漠里
is that we're both standing in the desert,
而你不能只带着一鞋底的沙子出去
and you can't leave with nothing to show but sand in your shoes.
我同意削减防御  跟之前的条件一样
I'll agree to the scale-back. Same terms as before.
你多快能开始撤军
How soon can you mobilize a withdrawal?
联合国军队一撤  我们也会撤的
Well, the moment UN forces begin to pull out, we will do the same.
我已让五角大楼
I've had the Pentagon
制定了一个最早明天就能执行的
come up with an exit plan that we can put into effect
撤退计划  至于其他联合国军队
as early as tomorrow. As for the rest of the UN forces,
我可以马上联系联合国秘书长
I can reach out to the Secretary General immediately.
你  还是你妻子
You or... your wife?
当然  她大概会代表我去打电话
Well, yes, she would probably make the call on my behalf.
我觉得还是不要了
I don't think she should.
你想让我打电话吗
You think I should make the call?
不止如此
More than that.
我觉得她该走人
I think she should be gone.
什么意思  不再参加谈判吗
Gone in what way? Gone from these negotiations?
不再做大使
As ambassador.
这是我最后的条件
My final condition.
这不能拿来商量
That cannot be on the table.
能  而且没得商量
It is. And it's non-negotiable.
邓普西女士  我是丽萨的朋友
Ms. Dempsey. I'm a friend of Lisa's.
-麦克斯  -对
- Uh, Max? - That's right.
她叫我告诉你  她要晚一会儿
Yes, she told me to tell you she's running a few minutes behind.
好  那我在外面等  谢谢
Okay, I'll just wait outside. Thank you.
不  外面太冷
No, it's... chilly.
进来去她房间吧
You can come on up to her room.
好
Okay.
我只想说  我很遗憾
I just want you to know... I'm so sorry.
丽萨告诉我们了  我们都为你祈祷
Lisa told us and our prayers are with you.
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
她说您和丈夫就像她父母  的确不难看出
She said you and your husband  were like parents to her. I see why.
请进
Come on in.
麦克斯
Max, hey.
抱歉我迟了
Sorry I'm late.
给  拿回去吧
Here, I want you to take that back.
不不  这钱是给你的
No, no, no, that money's yours.
不  我不能接受
No, I can't. I can't take it.
团契的人一起凑的
Everyone at the fellowship pitched in.
-还给他们吧  -我不能
- Just give it back to 'em. - I can't.
你说你需要钱买药的
You said that you needed the money for the medicine.
坐下吧
Yeah, sit down.
抱歉  请坐
Sorry, please.
好吧
Okay.
我要跟你说的事  听上去会很糟糕
What I'm about to tell you is gonna sound fucked up,
但你说什么之前  先听我说完  好吗
but just hear me out before you say anything, all right?
好
Okay.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
再也不回来了
And I'm not coming back.
我要走  是因为我有危险
And... I have to leave because I'm in danger.
我不叫麦克斯
My name isn't Max.
我也没有艾滋
I don't have AIDS.
-等等  -听我说完  拜托了
- Wait. Hold on. - Let me finish, please.
我想向你解释一切  但我不能
I want to explain everything to you, but I can't.
你知道得越少越好
The less you know, the better.
但听我说
But listen to me.
如果联调局找来  你什么都不能说
If the FBI comes here, you can't say anything.
你得告诉他们你不认识我
You have to tell them you don't know me.
-联调局  -对  如果他们找来
- The FBI? - Yes, and if they do,
你去联系这个人  他叫道格·斯坦普
I want you to contact this man. His name is Doug Stamper.
-他能帮你  -麦克斯  这太疯狂了
- And he can help you. - Max. This is crazy.
那不是我的名字
It's not my name.
是我编的  我编造了一切
I made it up. I made up everything.
名字  女友  诊所
The name, the girlfriend, the clinic.
不  我也去了
No, I was there with you.
我装的  我没办法
I faked it. I had to.
如果你不是麦克斯  你是谁
If you're not Max... then who are you?
拿着  他会帮你
Take this. He will help you.
他能保护你
He can protect you.
求你  我知道这不公平
Please. I know it's not fair.
-你走吧  -你得收下这个
- Please leave. - Let me leave this with you.
我跟这一切毫无关系
I don't want to have anything to do with it.
你拿走吧
Please, just take it with you.
你走吧
Please leave.
你是个好人  丽萨
You're a good person, Lisa.
但我不是
I'm just not.
很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
除了她  我还能给你什么
What can I offer you instead of her?
没了
Nothing.
人道主义救济金呢
What about a humanitarian relief fund,
给你在非洲的盟友
for your allies in Africa?
你可以随意使用
You can distribute it any way you see fit.
几十亿美元吗  我没那么好收买
A few billion dollars? I'm not that easily bought.
那我们重新考虑伊兹密尔的基地呢
All right, let's say that we re-examine our base in Izmir.
国会不会允许的
Congress would never let you.
而且现实点说
And realistically,
你愿意拿重要战略性空港
you're willing to barter major strategic airfields
交换你妻子吗
on account of your wife?
你不能把这事扯到她身上
You can't make this about her.
她本来就没资格做大使
She was never equipped to be an ambassador.
你很清楚
You know that.
我理解
I understand.
你怎么能拒绝自己的妻子呢
How could you say no to your own wife?
但她让你蒙蔽了双眼
But she's blinding you.
-我是在帮你忙  -你这是小心眼
- I'm doing you a favor. - You are being petty.
你派去的海豹突击队
The SEAL team you sent.
看我们多容易就耍了她
Look how easily we manipulated her.
莫里科夫都没怎么下功夫
Moryakov didn't have to work too hard.
我们是不是炸死了自家战士
Did we blow up our own men?
或许吧
Maybe we did.
或许没有
Maybe we didn't.
但我们让她以为我们做了
But we made her believe that we did.
而她说服了你
And she convinced you.
这不叫被蒙蔽吗
Now, wouldn't you call that blindness?
你现在想杀了我  我看得出
You want to kill me now. I can see it.
我读过一篇有趣的文章
I read an amusing article about, um...
一个内战情景重现演员
a Civil War re-enactor,
他说你的曾曾祖父
who said that your great-great-grandfather
赤手杀了一名北方兵
killed a Yankee soldier with his bare hands.
我在阿富汗时  我们被圣战组织偷袭了
When I was in Afghanistan, we were ambushed by the Mujahideen.
那个打中我这里和这里的人
And the man who shot me here and here,
他的枪卡住后  还刺了我一刀
he stabbed me when his rifle jammed.
我把刀拔了出来  割了他的喉
I pulled the knife away and slit his throat.
知道  这故事你跟媒体说过十多次了
Yes, I know, you've told that story dozens of times to the press.
但我没说的是
The part I don't tell is
我割了他喉咙之后  我并没停下
that after I slit his throat, I kept going.
我们把他的头绑在一头驴上
We strapped his head to a donkey
让驴把他的头带回他的村子
so it would carry it back to his village.
我赤手空拳杀过人
I've killed a man with my bare hands.
那不是故事
It wasn't make-believe.
你觉得你能做到吗
Do you think you're capable?
我觉得你能
I think you are.
你无情
You're ruthless.
跟我一样
Like me.
有时候对恨我们的人  我们必须无情
Sometimes we must be ruthless with those who hate us.
有时候对我们爱的人  也要无情
And sometimes we must be ruthless with those we love.
我不明白你为什么那么在乎克莱尔
I don't see why Claire means so much to you.
因为你非常在乎她
Because she means so much to you.
你如果答应  我就知道你是真心的
And if you do this, I will know you're serious.
您妻子打来了  先生
Your wife is on the line, sir.
告诉她我再回电
Tell her I'll call her back.
我已经说两次了
I've told her that twice now.
-再说  -是  先生
- Tell her again. - Yes, sir.
你不用洗的  萨拉
You don't have to do that, Sarah.
没事  不费事的
I don't mind. It doesn't take long.
没事  我们洗吧  你去放松
No, no. Let us do it. You go relax.
我待会儿就抱俩小坏蛋上床
I'll move the monsters in a few minutes.
-好  -好
- Okay. - All right.
床上见
See you in bed.
明天见
See you tomorrow.
真希望我能睡那么香
I wish I could sleep like that.
你考虑过成家吗
You ever think of settling down?
自己也生俩孩子
Gettin' a couple of these for yourself?
从没想过
Hasn't ever crossed my mind.
从没
Never?
这不适合我  这种生活
It's not for me. A life like that.
我这种生活吗
You mean a life like mine?
-我没那么说  -我知道你一直这么想
- That's not what I said. - I know you've always felt that way.
房贷  朝九晚五  妻子  俩孩子  一条狗
A mortgage, nine to five, wife, two kids, a dog.
不是
No.
我就是重视自由
It's just my freedom's important to me.
我比你自由多了  伙计
I'm freer than you are, pal.
我待在哥伦布是因为喜欢
I stayed in Columbus because I liked it,
又不是有谁逼我
not because anybody made me.
我选择了扎根
I chose to put down roots.
而你一直在逃避
You've always been running from something.
我可没对你指手画脚  你也别来说我
Hey, I don't judge you. Don't judge me.
就听你哥哥说一句
Listen to your big brother for a second.
不  我现在最不需要的就是教训
No, last thing I need is a lecture right now.
你整个恢复期间
During your whole recovery,
一直说着要回去工作
all you kept talking about was getting back to work.
我来了一个月
Over a month I've been here,
用我自己的假期  还请了假
using all my vacation time and then some.
你如果不想来  那就回家啊
If you don't want to be here, then maybe you should go home.
不是为这个  道格
It's not about that, Doug.
我来是因为你是我的亲人
I'm here because you're family.
因为你比工作更重要
Because you're more important than work.
我要是因为你丢了工作  我就另找个
If I lost my job because of you, I'd find another one.
你有什么
What do you have?
弗兰克·安德伍德吗  这你都没有
Frank Underwood? You don't even have that.
你冰箱上有两张照片
You got two pictures on your fridge,
还是我的孩子
and they're of my kids.
这不叫自由
That's not freedom.
佩特罗夫要求外交人事变动
Petrov wants a diplomatic change.
联合国的人事
At the UN.
-我  -没得商量
- Me. - It was non-negotiable.
你显然没有拒绝
Clearly, you didn't say no.
我想先跟你商量
I wanted to discuss it with you first.
我打了好几次
I called more than once.
我想说服自己拒绝他
I wanted to convince myself to refuse what he asked.
但我做不到
But... I couldn't do that.
我就说你去是在犯错  弗兰西斯
I told you it was a mistake to go, Francis.
决议案也是错呢  科里根也是个错误
And the resolution was a mistake. And Corrigan was a mistake.
我们可以一个个细数错误  但情况就是这样
We could tally up all our mistakes, but we are where we are.
我现在得专心解决眼前的问题
I need to concentrate on what's in front of me right now.
我  我就在你眼前
I am. I'm in front of you.
俄国必须撤军  就这么简单
The Russians need to leave. It's as simple as that.
你要我说这样没事
You want me to say this is okay.
不
No.
弗兰西斯  我更希望
Francis, I would've preferred
你直接走进来  告诉我我被解雇了
if you had walked in and just told me I was fired.
他们耍了你  克莱尔
They played you, Claire.
莫里科夫根本不是良心发现
Moryakov was not having some crisis of conscience.
全是为了骗我们派海豹突击队去
It was all so that we would send our SEAL team in.
好让我们激怒以色列
So that we would provoke the Israelis.
我没看出来  因为我太信任你了
And I didn't see it, because I trusted you too much.
我没能客观地思考
I didn't look at it objectively...
因为你是我妻子
because you're my wife.
-佩特罗夫说的  -是
- Petrov told you that? - Yes.
-你相信他  -是的
- And you believe him? - I do.
我会辞职
I'll resign.
真希望不用走到这一步
I wish it didn't have to come to this.
我们怎么跟媒体说
What do we say to the press?
你想专注于竞选
That you want to focus on the campaign,
本来就如此打算
that that was your plan all along.
但我想先看到危机解决
That I want to see this crisis through, first.
没人会质疑的
No one will question that.
告诉佩特罗夫
Tell Petrov.
我会
And I will...
在你需要的时候宣布
make the announcement whenever you want me to.
克莱尔
Claire.
你说得对  我不该去
You were right. I shouldn't have gone.
那是你该做的决定  不是我
It was your decision to make. Not mine.
晚安
Good night.
我的决定
My decision.
有时候我觉得总统之位
Sometimes I think the presidency...
是有选择的假象
is the illusion of choice.
怎么了
What is it?
我得去白宫
I have to go to the White House.
这大半夜的
It's the middle of the night.
他是总统啊
He's the president.
谢谢  密查姆
Thank you, Meechum.
坐吧
Have a seat.
我吵醒你了
I wake you up?
没事
It's fine.
反正我睡觉不实
I'm a light sleeper anyway.
就算不是你  警笛  垃圾车也能吵醒我
If it wasn't you, it would've been a siren or a dump truck.
我经常大半夜被吵醒
I get woken up in the middle of the night all the time.
世界什么地方出现危机了
Some crisis somewhere in the world.
战况室
Some... situation...
出现了什么情况
in the Situation Room.
比垃圾车好多了
Well, that's better than a dump truck.
你去找了蒂姆·科贝特
You reached out to Tim Corbet.
是啊
I did.
我几天前跟他通了话
I spoke to him a few days ago.
他专程打来通知我
He called to let me know.
那么你俩很亲密了
So you two are still close.
现在不是了
Not anymore.
在学校时是很亲密
At school we were.
我觉得他可能知道你当时是什么样子
I thought he might have some insight to how you were back then.
渐渐成熟起来的时期
Those are formative years.
可能对你更有价值
More formative for you than for me.
我也就是学会了走正步和开枪
I learned how to march and shoot a gun, that's about it.
我要是去了军事学院的确会更好
I would've been better off in military school.
是吗  为什么
Yeah? Why's that?
还不到合法喝酒的年纪  就从男妓
You go from turning tricks to being on the bestseller list
一跃成为畅销书作家  这对人没好处
before you can legally drink, it messes with you.
你告诉我是你朋友...
You told me your friend was the one who, uh...
我撒谎了
I lied.
为什么  觉得耻辱吗
Why? You ashamed?
我第一次那么做  简直吓死了
First time I did it, I was scared out of my mind.
我敲门  门开了
I knock on the door, it opens...
那人穿了缎子睡袍
guy's in a satin robe.
他很胖
He's fat.
头发粘粘的  梳过来盖住了秃顶的地方
Stringy hair, combed over his bald spot.
脸上汗如雨下
Beads of sweat rolling down his cheeks.
我差点掉头跑回电梯了
I almost ran back to the elevator.
但你没有
But you didn't.
没有
No.
我需要钱
I needed the money.
我脱衣服之前
Before I got undressed...
他告诉我他妻子刚死了
he tells me that his wife just died.
车祸
Car accident.
他说他们本打算春天去东京玩
Says they had plans to visit Tokyo in the spring.
还跟我说起了他的三个孩子
Tells me about his three kids.
有一个生来唇腭裂
The one that was born with a cleft palate.
描述了他韦斯切斯特的房子
Describes his house in Westchester,
有阳台  有起居室
with a Juliet balcony in the living room.
还说她是多么美
Says how beautiful she was.
告诉我他不想死
Tells me he doesn't want to die.
根本没碰我
Never touched me once.
有时候只是性
Sometimes it was just sex.
但更多时候不是的
But a lot of times, it wasn't.
他们什么都告诉我
They would tell me everything.
这些人
These men.
那种窥视
That access.
那些秘密
Those stories.
让人上瘾
It was an addiction.
我渴望它
I craved it.
我期盼它
I lived for it.
然后你给写下来
And then you wrote about it.
我成名后
When I got famous...
我只能收手
I had to stop.
我又做了一次  被人认了出来
I tried it once, I got recognized.
我不再是透明人了
I wasn't invisible anymore.
我无法逃离自己
I couldn't escape myself.
有时候  我希望我也能做到
I wish I could do that sometimes.
逃离自己
Escape myself.
是因为克莱尔吗
Is it Claire?
你叫我来不是为了蒂姆·科贝特
You didn't ask me here to talk about Tim Corbet.
你有什么好处
What's in this for you?
我上瘾
I'm addicted.
对我吗
To me?
我背叛了她
I betrayed her.
怎么回事
How?
我不是作为你的传记作者问你
I'm not asking as your biographer.
我是作为你的朋友问你
I'm asking as your friend.
我们是朋友吗
Are we friends?
我们可以装成朋友
We could pretend to be.
这不是装
This isn't pretend.
我是真的
I'm real.
你在伤心
You're hurting.
她更伤心
She's hurting more.
人人都有伤心事
Everyone's hurting.
回家吧
Go home.
去睡会儿
You should get some sleep.
我也该睡了
And so should I.
三十年时间不短啊
Thirty years is a long time.
你们都走到这一步了
You've made it this far.
好啦
Okay!
双重攻击
Double!
天呐
Jesus.
我没听到你回来
I didn't hear you come back.
我不想吵你
I didn't want to wake you.
-怎么了  -中东分局
- What is it? - Mid-East bureau.
说俄国人撤军了
They say the Russians are pulling out their troops.
他的努力显然是成功了
Whatever he did out there must have worked.
不知道他付出了什么
I wonder what it cost him.
我们找了两个焦点小组做调查
We ran the different looks by a couple of focus groups.
这三个扮相最受欢迎
These are the three favorites.
这个不要
Not this one.
这个吧  怎么样
Uh, this one. What do you think?
我喜欢
I like it.
-发色也要染吗  -介意回归金发吗
- The hair color as well? - Do you mind going back to blonde?
我更喜欢深色
I'd prefer it dark.
焦点小组  尤其是爱荷华州的  喜欢金发
The groups, in Iowa, in particular, they like the blonde.
好吧  那就金发
Fine. We'll go blonde then.
你在女性中深受欢迎
You're popular among women.
我们想尽可能提高支持率
We want to push those numbers as high as we can,
一点一滴都很重要
and every little bit counts.
你不用解释  宣布辞职后
You don't have to explain. We'll do the color change
就染发
after we announce the resignation.
谢谢  艾伯
Thanks, Abbie.
如果你不想  就不必这么做
If you don't want to, you don't have to do this.
没事
It's fine.
提不提名  不会靠你的头发
The nomination is not gonna hinge on your hair.
你听到艾伯的话了  一点一滴都很重要
You heard what Abbie said. Every little bit counts.
我们做我们该做的
We'll do what we have to.
奥巴马刚刚就任不久  就在讲话中对巴勒斯坦流露出许多同情
令盟友以色列政府大为光火
2011年  由于不满奥巴马的讲话  到华盛顿访问的以色列总理内塔尼亚胡
在记者面前对奥巴马很不客气  大段大段地讲述中东历史
把美国总统当作小学生一般
随后在G20峰会上  奥巴马同法国总统萨科齐
私下抱怨内塔尼亚胡的言论意外曝光
记者听到萨科齐指责内塔尼亚胡是"说谎者"
而奥巴马则无奈地回答
"你受够了他  可我还不得不每天跟他打交道"
这段对话曝光后  奥巴马同内塔尼亚胡的关系更是跌至冰点
最近一段时间  由于以色列反对白宫同伊朗正在进行的谈判
美以关系愈发紧张
今年年初  内塔尼亚胡接受众议院议长博纳的邀请到美国国会发表演讲
但是由于这个安排事先没有知会白宫  令奥巴马大为光火
遂以"不在外国领导人选举前举行国事会见"为由
拒绝在内塔尼亚胡来访时同他会面
同时在白宫的支持下
国会大批民主党议员也借故决定不出席内塔尼亚胡的演讲
白宫也把副总统拜登和国务卿克里安排到国外访问
这样内塔尼亚胡3月初到访美国时
只能去国会山给半个国会做个演讲
白宫却要把他拒之门外